presentjobs.com 2018-08-23

# Privacy Policy - Present Jobs - Jobs For Freshers & Experienced | Fresher Jobs | Fresher Walkins

**Please read carefully the below privacy policy of presentjobs.com**

**By using presentjobs.com you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions :**

**The information collected by our services :**  
We may collect our website visitor’s system information such as IP Address, Location, Operating System or Browser Type.  This is a partial list, however all this collected information is used only to know about user preferences and to make improvements to our service. presentjobs does not sell or share this information to any other websites, third-parties or agents either directly or indirectly.

When you register with our website, we may collect the users personal information such as name, address, contact number, email address. However most of the details are optional. presentjobs does not sell or share this information  to any other websites, third- parties or agents either directly or indirectly.

**No Spam activities:**

As part of our services, Presentjobs.com sends daily job emails to our users registered for our services. However the users can change their email preferences or unsubscribe at any time. Every mail sent by us includes the ‘Un-Subscribe’ link at the end of the job mails sent by us. Presentjobs.com does not involve in transmission of any ‘junk mails’, ‘chain emails’ or ‘spamming’.

**Cookies and Web beacons:**

We may access and set cookies using Web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs, which are invisible graphical images. These Web beacons tell us useful information regarding our site such as which pages users access. However we use this information only for the purpose of improving our services.

**IMP Note :**  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
– You can [Check Here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) to know more details about DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Third Party Advertisements

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies (such as Google’s Adsense) may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. It could also access and set cookies in your browser, use web beacons as mentioned above. For further information, please consult the [Privacy Policy of Google (Adsense)](https://www.google.com/privacy.html).

**Privacy policy subject to change:**

The above privacy policy is subject to change. We would be communicating to the user either by email or by updating the policy at the presentjobs website. In case of any doubt, you may clarify our policies by referring to our website or by directly contacting us.

Users / Others are encouraged to contact us for any privacy related queries at  **admin (at) presentjobs (dot) com**
